Earvin James Dantes

earvinjamesdantes@gmail.com / +639065807055 / 0009 Riverside Subd. Brgy. Calitcalit, San Juan, Batangas, .

Summary

I am a self-taught Software Engineer that is eager, responsible, and hardworking. Working on several projects assisted me in adapting to changes and shaped me into a team-player. I am able to work well in a team setting while still exercising my initiative. I am able to operate well under pressure and meet tight deadlines. I am experienced in frontend development as well as back-end development. I am mainly a web developer, developer, but I also do mobile development.

Experience

Junior Full Stack Developer Intern

Offshorly

05/2022 - Present

- Was the lead full-stack developer of a leaderboard application specifically for the -Le games (Nerdle, Wordle, Quordle, etc.). The technologies that we used were ReactJS, NodeJS, React Native, AWS, DynamoDB
- Helped with the development of a procurement application for a UK company. The technologies that we used were ReactJS, NodeJS, AWS, DynamoDB

Full Stack Developer Intern

Quadrologix • Batangas City, Calabarzon

02/2021 - 05/2021

- Worked on developing a scalable API for a Flutter application using Django together with a team of 5.
- Developed the UI using Flutter with an MVC approach
- Developed high quality websites for clients using React

Software Developer Trainee

Innospire Corporation • Batangas City, Calabarzon

10/2019 - 11/2019

- Developed websites for clients using PHP and MySQL.
- Created high quality designs (logos, slogans, etc.) using Adobe Photoshop.

Skills

JavaScript, ReactJS, HTML, CSS, Git, Flutter, Node.js, Python, Django, Dart, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

Education

Information Technology

Batangas State University • Batangas City, Calabarzon 05/2024

Currently a sophomore at the university. I'm keeping up with my academics, and working well with my classmates. Being present and involved in my classes, and being open to learn on what the courses have in stored